[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 9]
Are you a god?
I am a demon.
Gods aren't the only ones
who can grant your wish.
Demons can do it too.
There must be a price, right?
Of course.
I'm willing.
Aren't you going to ask
what the price is?
I'm willing
no matter the price.
God,
Bodhisattva,
I wish for my illness to disappear,
for me to become stronger.
Let me help my sister
so that she won't have to carry the burden alone.
May my sister
be a happy, free,
and unrestrained woman.
May I no longer be a bystander
and instead share the burden.
Look.
His wish was so strong.
He was sick,
but he was determined.
Everything he did
was just to live on
to share your burden
and give you freedom.
But you...
You suspected him
and humiliated him.
He wanted to take the bow and arrow to share your burden.
But in the end,
he died under your bow.
Do you deserve
being called his sister?
Shut up!
You want to kill me?
Just like
how you killed your brother?
Just let go.
But what's the use of killing me?
You're just venting your anger
and deceiving yourself.
It was I
who helped him realize his wish,
while you
kept saying you were acting for his own good,
but you made him suffer so much.
He would rather be a demon
than be a human.
Pei Sijing,
your arrow
shouldn't point at me.
It should point at yourself.
A heartless person
also has tears?
Does Pei Siheng know you cried for him?
Have you ever felt guilty
in the days and nights after his death?
Have you ever,
for even a moment,
truly understood him?
Until his death,
the last words you left for him were...
You've committed countless sins.
You are unforgivable.
I was wrong.
Actually,
you feel guilty too.
You want to
personally apologize to Heng,
right?
Yes.
I owe him this.
I can take you to Heng
and let you apologize
in person.
Pei Sijing,
are you willing?
Sister Pei!
Sister Pei, don't trust him!
Sister Pei, let me in!
Sister Pei!
Are you willing?
How?
How do I open this?
I...
am willing.
♫Someday I'll return to my old hometown♫
♫Wearing old clothes but with eyes shining bright♫
♫Holding brilliance in the right hand♫
♫Biting down on all panic♫
♫Wiping away frost with the left hand♫
♫I finally look up♫
♫You're in front of me♫
Sister Pei!
I fulfilled your wish,
but you repaid me with betrayal.
Sister Pei.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
Your brother's nature is pure and kind.
He must have been tricked by this weasel
and that's why he became a demon.
He is the culprit.
Sister.
Why didn't you come to see me?
You turned me into this.
Sister.
I missed you.
Nonsense.
If you really hate your sister,
you wouldn't want her forgiveness.
I'm indeed sinful
and unforgivable.
But Sister,
I know I was wrong
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫I'm a black-and-white wound♫
But she still...
♫You're the vibrant red color♫
personally killed her own brother.
♫How can I not remember♫
♫You're always by my side♫
She never asked him why
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
or showed any pity.
♫Guarding the memories, never fading away♫
Her actions were swift
and her heart was firm.
You said she has no heart.
But do you think Sister Pei is happy?
She lives in pain and self-blame every day.
It's fake.
It's merely to ease
her conscience.
I don't know what's fake.
I only know you both don't say what you mean.
You always call me a child,
but even I am more honest than you.
You adults
easily say hurtful words,
but you hide your love in your heart.
Instead of being insincere,
the truth is what you should say,
right?
Mother, I don't understand.
Bai Jiu, you're still young.
Of course you don't understand.
But in this world,
love and hate coexist.
Often, just a slight difference in thought
can produce hatred from love,
and become an obsession.
This obsession
then becomes hatred.
This hatred
contains
deep love.
Heng.
Do you hate me?
I hate myself more.
Ridiculous.
In this world,
it is hard to distinguish between gratitude and resentment.
It is hard to erase love and hate.
All sincerity
will be betrayed.
Pei Siheng.
The person who killed you is right in front of you.
Take
your revenge.
You are indeed from a family of demon hunters.
Your brother can't defeat you.
Let me try.
Zhi Mei.
Zhi Mei is the most popular candidate
for the top courtesan of Tianxiang Pavilion.
You're well-informed, Mr. Zhuo.
I just didn't expect it.
You're so strict and orderly usually,
but you actually have such refined interests.
My refined interest
is killing demons that yap.
The annual courtesan selection of Tianxiang Pavilion
has caused a stir in Tiandu.
It's hard not to know.
Zhi Mei was unpopular before.
Now,
she's overwhelming the other competitors.
It means Cheng Huang has indeed fulfilled her wish.
Cheng Huang controlled Zhi Mei's puppet to kill,
setting up Cheng Huang's formation,
and absorbing the power of life.
Zhi Mei and the puppet are one.
The puppet absorbed the vitality of the living.
Zhi Mei
naturally regained her youthful beauty too.
If the murderer was Zhi Mei's puppet,
why was it Pei Siheng at the crime scene?
Or
was the Pei Siheng here
also a puppet?
I saw plum blossom petals
at the crime scene.
Look at the plum blossom petals
all over the stage.
It means the killer was indeed
Zhi Mei's puppet.
Maybe Pei Siheng
was only sent by Cheng Huang to save Zhi Mei's puppet.
There are no plum trees in the yard.
Where did these petals come from?
The plates are still warm.
That means
the murderer is still here.
Before, we didn't understand
why Pei Siheng became a demon
and why he came back to life.
Now we understand.
Pei Siheng
must have made a wish to Cheng Huang too.
You're indeed made of wood.
Sister is in danger.
Go save her!
Sister Pei!
Zhu Yan.
Surprised?
Old geezer.
I'm quite surprised.
I didn't expect
you're still as impolite as before.
you would have hooked up with Li Lun.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is that sundial
Li Lun's precious treasure?
Yes.
So what?
Based on my understanding of Li Lun,
he won't give it to you for no reason.
Tell me.
What shameful deal did you two make?
Isn't the malicious energy on Zhao Yuanzhou
enough?
No.
How do you know so much?
Here.
I keep my word.
Since you know him so well,
why don't you take a guess?
To make you open the Kunlun Gate,
right?
Good guess.
Only demons like me
who have lived for tens of thousands of years
can do it.
Who is it?
A friend from the Demon Hunting Bureau?
I'll lend you the Truth Eye
and let you remember
what I look like.
Who are you?
Are you Ying Zhao's grandson?
You know me?
Of course.
I was taken care of Ying Zhao before,
so I don't want to hurt you.
Get out of my way.
Since I was asked to guard here,
I won't let anyone
inside.
With just you?
Cheng Huang.
You're an old demon who's lived for tens of thousands of years.
Instead of retiring,
you came to the mortal world without permission
and killed the innocent.
Do you admit your crime?
You have the power of the Qiankun,
yet you killed the innocent.
Do you admit your crime?
You are…
Baize Goddess?
Yes.
I'm here to capture you today.
Return to the Demon Hunting Bureau to be punished.
Evil?
I'm helping them realize their wishes.
You look for those with a wish
and bewitch them,
turning them into puppets.
Then you manipulate the puppets to kill
and absorb other people's lives
to fulfill their wishes.
If this isn't evil, then what is it?
I can grant your wish.
Are you willing?
[Tavern]
That's right.
Actually, the one who was killing
was not your brother,
but the puppet I made.
Kill this puppet and take revenge!
You've always been cold-hearted.
Let me see
if you can
do it now too.
Sister Pei.
I'm going to kill you
to avenge my brother!
Heng is my masterpiece.
I was very satisfied,
so I took him as my disciple.
Unfortunately,
Heng doesn't listen to me anymore.
It's useless to keep him.
But now it seems
you still can't bear to kill him.
How about
I help you?
Brother!
Even the Original Goddess couldn't do anything to me.
You,
with only half of the Baize Token,
think you can order me to stop?
I'm old now.
I feel tired when I move.
I'm not in the mood
to play with you kids anymore.
Since you like staying in the sundial so much,
you can stay
until the end of the world.
Heng.
Before,
I wondered countless times
if you would cry
for me when I died.
Why wouldn't I?
Of course I would.
Because you are my brother.
You've always been
cold and distant since childhood.
I never understood your emotions.
When I was young,
I got angry and said
that even if I died,
you wouldn't shed a single tear for me.
But now,
I realized
I don't want you to cry at all.
Sister.
Don't cry.
I don't deserve you to cry for me.
Heng.
I'm sorry.
If...
If I could let you finish back then...
Back then,
I only...
Don't blame yourself.
I didn't kill them,
but I caused the disaster.
It was me.
I killed so many innocent people.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I just want you
to forgive me.
Don't blame me.
Sister.
After I die,
♫I guard the eaves♫
I won't be able to do anything for you anymore.
♫And watch the times fade♫
♫You hold the flame and watch the night♫
Heng
♫I count the winters♫
What else can I do for you
♫And waited for one more year♫
♫My heart is full of passion♫
Good
Good.
Live
♫The stars dazzle and the crescent moon curves♫
And
♫The guilty greed♫
♫Thousands of dark hairs, long and short♫
Heng.
♫The cruel entanglement♫
Don't leave me.
♫Lend me the cold lamp for one night♫
♫Let regret stay before dawn♫
Heng.
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫In the sky of floating snowflakes♫
♫You are the only warm bloom♫
♫But why don't I remember♫
♫How much the plot has twisted?♫
♫I forgot the bitter karma♫
♫I missed it again and again♫
♫Helpless♫
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫I'm a black-and-white wound♫
♫You're the vibrant red color♫
♫How can I not remember♫
♫You're always by my side♫
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
♫Guarding the memories, never fading away♫
Cheng Huang said we're going to stay here
until the end of the world.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
what should we do?
He's the one who controls the sundial.
If he won't show up,
it's indeed troublesome.
Appear.
I hope I can
pass the imperial examination
and become an official who pleads for the people.
I hope I can find my true love
and be together forever.
If I can give birth to my child,
I will repay you for my wish.
It's a normal puppet without memories.
This puppet...
What?
I've seen her
in the album of past goddesses that my master gave me.
She was the Original Goddess.
The Original Goddess?
You didn't know?
Just now,
Cheng Huang mentioned it.
I'm so young.
How would I know?
I didn't exist
when the Original Goddess appeared.
Only an old monster like Cheng Huang
would have met the Original Goddess.
Then why does Cheng Huang have a puppet of the Original Goddess?
Could it be
she also had a wish that she couldn't tell
and was cheated by Cheng Huang?
The goddess's wish
was peace between the two realms,
for kindness and evil to have consequences,
and for bad demons like Cheng Huang to be punished.
How could she be cheated by him?
But
it's evident
that Cheng Huang treated this puppet
very differently.
The paint on it was retouched
after it faded.
It's exquisite.
Hmm...
I got it.
Let's use this puppet as a hostage.
Old thing,
I'll count down from three.
If you don't come out,
I'll destroy this puppet
and twist off her head.
Three.
Two.
One.
If you don't come out,
I'll kiss her.
Ridiculous.
This is an emergency.
It calls for desperate tactics.
This tactic is too desperate.
The desperateness is too tacky.
Are you really not coming out?
You bastard!
Give it back!
Otherwise, none of you can get out.
Well,
I'm not in a hurry to go out.
I just want to hear some legendary gossip.
What's your relationship
with the Original Goddess?
How could a heartless demon
have anything to do with the goddess?
Why not?
Didn't the cruelest demon in the world
also call Zhao Wan'er his sister?
How can you compare with me?
Wan'er and I were really like siblings.
But you...
You secretly painted the goddess's puppet
but cut back on the fabric,
making her seem a bit frivolous.
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
Stop!
Shut up or stop?
Zhu Yan.
Brother Zhuo!
Brother Zhuo.
We came out of the illusion.
I don't think so.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
where are we?
This mountain and stone
is the way from the Wilderness to the Kunlun Gate.
But this is not the Wilderness.
It's just a replica of the Wilderness.
We're still in Cheng Huang's illusion.
Why did you
invite us here?
Didn't you want to know
about the Original Goddess?
No one wants to know
about your stupid love life.
Hurry up and—
I want to know.
The original Baize Token
was divided into two.
The Original Goddess
and the strongest Great Demon of the Wilderness
managed it together.
After the ancient flood,
the gods fell.
The human and demon worlds
fell into chaos.
I was ordered by White Emperor Shaohao
to rule the demons in the Wilderness
and protect all beings.
But as destined by fate,
I, Baize, am a celestial beast
and am immortal,
but I’m willing to sacrifice myself
and transform into the power of Baize
to be passed on in the world.
Each generation, I will choose
the purest human
to control all demons.
Bless everything.
Invulnerable to all evil.
We promise to work together
and guard the Wilderness.
And guard the Wilderness.